So I'm just wondering what you could say about, like,
所以我想问问，你能不能聊聊，
the whole situation leading up to,
整件事一路发展到现在，
like more of the behind the scenes,
比如更多幕后的情况，
whatever you can kind of say on that.
你方便说的都可以聊聊。
I know a lot of people,
我知道很多人，
including myself, are very curious as to
包括我自己，都非常好奇
what made that decision,
到底是什么原因让他们做出这个决定，
you know, get happen, really.
说白了，这事到底是怎么发生的。
Yeah, I mean, everything...
对，我的意思是，整件事……
started, or not started, but I found out everything
也不是说从那时开始吧，但我是从那时候
during IEM Rio.
得知这一切的，在 IEM 里约 期间。
I mean, I arrived in Rio and
我是说，我刚到里约，
the same day, in the evening, I just
就在同一天晚上，
got a message from the manager that we need to talk,
经理就给我发消息，说我们得谈谈。
and I knew it's not going to be a nice talk
我当时就知道，这肯定不会是什么好谈话，
because of the way he said it.
从他说话的那个方式我就感觉到了。
There was never discussion in the team about
队里之前从来没有讨论过
doing changes or
要换人，
doing anything like that, so it was
或者做类似的调整，所以这件事对我来说
super random for me.
真的是非常突然。
Yes, like, I mean,
对，就是，我的意思是，
I'm aware,
我知道，
and everyone is aware that we were not playing
而且所有人都知道，我们今年打得
our best game this year,
并不是最好的一段状态，
but...
但是……
this is a project that
这本来是一个
we wanted to build something long-term.
我们想长期去打造的项目。
It was not about winning an event now and
它本来就不是说现在立刻拿一个冠军，
like, we would feel like we accomplished everything,
然后就算把所有目标都完成了一样，
but this was something that we wanted to do for
而是我们本来就想把这套东西
a while, like this team was promised
长期做下去。因为这支队伍当初被承诺过
time, and we just wanted to build something
会有时间，我们也只是想把一些东西
long-term.
真正长期地建立起来。
And that's why it came out as a shock to me because
所以这件事才会让我这么震惊，因为
as I said, there were not any talks, at least on my side.
就像我说的，至少在我这边，之前没有过任何沟通。
I was never told, or I didn't have any talk with anyone
从来没有人提前告诉过我，我也没有和任何人
from the team or the organization
无论是队里还是俱乐部那边的人，
about something like this happening.
聊过会发生这种事。
And just the timing of it makes it even worse because
而且这件事发生的时间点，让情况变得更糟，
like, it was IEM Rio, and then there,
因为当时正好是 IEM Rio，然后接下来
like Falcons have two more events
Falcons 还要打两个比赛，
and then it's the Major,
再往后就是 Major 了，
so it's not hard,
所以这不是说很难，
but almost impossible to make the Major
而是几乎不可能赶上 Major，
because the roster lock was
因为 Major 的阵容锁定时间
during IEM Rio, so
就在 IEM Rio 期间，
it's basically impossible for me to play the Major.
所以我基本上不可能再去打这届 Major 了。
So yeah, I mean, it's not the best situation to be in, but...
所以，是啊，这肯定不是最理想的处境，但是……
I already accepted it, and I'm trying to move on, and
我已经接受了，我也在努力往前看，
we'll see what the future holds.
接下来就看未来会怎么发展吧。
The fact that it happened
尤其是这件事发生的时候，
while you're in the middle of a tournament,
你人还正在比赛中间，
I mean, like,
我的意思是，
that's gotta be hard
那肯定很难顶，
to be going into the server to click heads,
你还得进服务器继续对枪打头，
and in the back of your mind
但脑子后面又一直挂着
you're like, what the hell,
“这都什么鬼”的念头，
like, I'm not even a part of this team technically.
就好像严格来说，我都已经不算这支队的一员了。
How do you manage that? Like, that's crazy.
你是怎么撑住的？这也太夸张了。
It was really hard for me.
这对我来说真的很难。
I mean, I was still
我是说，我当时还是
obviously playing and trying to win every moment
一直在打，也一直想在每个时刻都争取赢下来，
during these 10 days in Rio.
在里约那 10 天里都是这样。
In the back of my head,
但在我脑子里，
I knew that I'm not part of this team anymore,
我也很清楚，我已经不再是这支队的一员了。
so I did my best.
所以我只能尽我所能。
I'm sad that we couldn't lift the trophy
我很遗憾我们没能捧起奖杯，
because it would've been a good story
因为那样的话，这会是一个很好的故事，
like, to end with,
一个很好的收尾。
but it was definitely hard, like hard to...
但那段时间确实很难，真的很难……
focus at some moments,
有些时候很难集中注意力，
even hard to find motivation in a way.
甚至某种程度上，很难找到继续打下去的动力。
It was hard to sleep, even,
甚至连睡觉都很难，
because of the news,
一方面是因为这个消息，
also because of the jet lag and all of that connected,
另一方面还有时差，所有这些事情都缠在一起，
you know, but yeah,
你也知道，就是这样吧。
it was not the best situation to be in, to be honest.
说实话，那绝对不是一个好受的处境。